[
  {
    "question": "Will I be rich?",
    "answer": "It is certain."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I find true love?",
    "answer": "It is decidedly so."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I win the lottery?",
    "answer": "Without a doubt."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I recieve a paid vacation soon?",
    "answer": "Yes - definitely."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I die soon?",
    "answer": "You may rely on it."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I retire early?",
    "answer": "As I see it, yes."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will Cognizant hire me?",
    "answer": "Reply hazy, try again."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will this web server crash?",
    "answer": "Ask again later."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will my wife be a millionaire?",
    "answer": "Don't count on it."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will you go out with me?",
    "answer": "My reply is no."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will I win the World Cup?",
    "answer": "Outlook not so good."
  }
]
